with what has happened now also the
con lo que ha pasado ahora también la
controversy that has happened in the last few
polémica que ha pasado en las últimas
hours Well of course A few days ago the news came out
horas Pues claro Hace unos días salió la
that the television factory was
noticia de que la fábrica de la tele ya
no longer going to work in media set It has
no iba a trabajar más en medias set
not yet been clarified When they
Todavía no se ha aclarado bien Cuándo
end How and so on because it
finalizan De qué manera y demás porque
is true that mediaset has
sí que es verdad que mediaset pues tiene
part of the television factory
parte de la fábrica de la tele en
specifically they own 30%
concreto son propietarios de un 30% por
therefore that 30% either they have to
lo tanto ese 30% o bien se lo tienen que
sell it to the television factory or I don't know
vender a la fábrica de la tele o no sé
how the move will be made there are still
de qué manera se hará la movida quedan
programs from the television factory still in
programas de la de la tele todavía en
media set there is
media set está
socialite there is
socialite está el de
Rito's There was another one no Or just those two I
Rito Había otro no O solo esos dos yo
think just those two not social and the one with
creo que solo esos dos no social y el de
risto socialite and the one with risto because
risto socialite y el de risto porque
risto now no no was with El Chester
risto ahora no no estaba con El Chester
again recently yes El Chester has started
otra vez hace poco sí ha empezado El
risto again s that one is also
Chester risto otra vez s ese también es
from the television factory so there are
de la fábrica de la tele entonces hay
some
algunos
How good what is being rumored
Que bueno lo que se está rumoreando
basically they want to keep social
básicamente que social lo quieren quedar
but they will keep it passing it to another
pero se lo quedan pasándolo a otra
production company to mandarina surely but
productora a mandarina seguramente pero
without María Patiño they want to keep it without
sin María Patiño quieren quedárselo sin
María Patiño  and María Patiño is super
María Patiño y está María Patiño super
upset she has spoken out and
disgustada que se ha pronunciado y ha
said the following in an interview that she
dicho lo siguiente en una entrevista que
officially gave, we don't
ha dado a lectura oficialmente no
know anything although
sabemos nada aunque desde hace poco ha
the phone started ringing recently there is nothing
empezado a sonar el teléfono no hay nada
concrete I am from the TV factory
concreto soy de la fábrica de la tele
until December I love live and
hasta diciembre me encanta el directo y
I don't know if I'm going to ask to continue doing it
yo no sé si voy a pedir seguir haciendo
or not anything could happen and I want to
o no puede pasar cualquier cosa y quiero
face it María Patiño is unemployed
afrontarlo María Patiño al paro
yes but she says until December December
sí pero dice hasta diciembre diciembre
María's contract with the TV factory ends Yes I think so yes I think they
María Sí yo creo que a r sí que creo que
want it not on tele5 they have said that they are
lo quieren no en tele5 han dicho que el
going to continue doing the risto program
programa de risto sí que lo van a seguir
that
haciendo que sí que quieren quedarse con
yes they want to keep risto that about that no I haven't heard anything I have said yes they know who is left that they have offered ristos and to keep everything in lies and yes yes that I have read to continue doing everything in lies and
leído seguir haciendo todo en mentira y
such with a lot Well but socializing is
tal con mucho Bueno pero socialicé
not bad either no socialito is bad it is
tampoco va mal no socialito va mal hace
an 11 a 10 an 11 what what how are
un 11 un 10 un 11 que que qué tal Y cómo
the audiences a 10 it's
están las audiencias un 10 es una
wonderful let's go at that hour and from the heart
maravilla vamos a esa hora y del corazón
no no  it's working badly let's do
no no está funcionando mal vamos hacer
the same as the data that throws a party
lo mismo que los datos que hace fiesta
more or less and the party continues but of course the
más o menos y fiesta sigue pero claro el
problem I think it's Maria Patiño who
problema Yo creo que es María Patiño que
wants it they want to take it away from there is
la quiere se la quieren quitar de ahí es
that you remove socialite and that you are going to
que tú quitas socialité y que vas a
put in a new one now from Zero and what
meter uno nuevo ahora de Cero y qué
happens is that for me socialite is the same as
pasa es que yo socialité es lo mismo que
a program it is at a time when there is nothing
un programa es a una hora donde no hay
you are waiting to watch the
nada tú estás esperando para ver las
news it is a weekend at
noticias es un fin de semana a la hora
lunchtime you put it on as background no of
de comer te lo pones como fondo no de
but Maria patio has made stag with
pero María patio ha hecho estag con
socialite with the program it is in lies
socialité con el programa es en mentiras
in stories in I mean it's like a
en historias en o sea es como un
filler program no I mean no yes total total I
programa relleno no O sea no sí total
think that yes they leave it there
total yo pienso que sí que lo dejan ahí
because to see it is not good [ __ ] it is a
pues para ver no está bien [__] es un
quick program of the heart like that of course
programa rapidito del corazón así claro
but it is the time of laida and the
pero que es la hora de laida y las
news but let's go if they don't put
noticias pero vamos que como no pongan
cartoons I do not see anything else
dibujos animados Yo es que no veo otra
that they are going to put there but Mara
cosa que van a poner ahí pero Mara
nothing quar with the idea but without Maria
nada quar con la idea pero sin María
patio with another person
patio con otra persona
not with Nuria Nuria Marín Maybe
no con Nuria Nuria Marín A lo mejor
because Nuria is not from the
porque Nuria no es de la fábrica de la
television factory I think that no no I think that
tele yo creo que no no s yo creo que
Nuria is not from the TV factory no
Nuria no es de la fábrica de la tele no
or yes well it's that of course all the
o sí bueno es que claro todos los
programs that Nuria has worked on from the factory Maybe she is from
programas que de la fábrica ha trabajado
yes she is
Nuria A lo mejor s que es de si que es
from the TV factory she has a contract
de la fábrica de la tele tiene contrato
with them I like it a lot I think it's
con ellos me gusta mucho creo
spontaneous I like it a lot too
que espontá a mí me gusta también mucho
Nuria notices that she likes the subject that she
Nuria nota que le gusta el tema de que
lives it she likes the subject yes Nuria
lo vive le gusta el tema sí Nuria lo
does it very well the image of María Patiño
hace muy bien la imagen de María Patiño
is already very damaged
ya está muy dañada
then people also want
entonces la gente también quiere caras
new faces And the thing is that I think that
nuevas Y es que yo creo que ya no se ve
the programs are not watched anymore after having made them
los programas después de haberlos hecho
eh Because I don't understand how she doesn't
eh Porque no lo entiendo como no se
correct herself sincerely Oh the poor thing Oh the
corrige sinceramente Ay la pobre Ay la
poor thing well the poor thing it makes me a little
pobre bueno la pobre a mí me da un poco
tender María Patiño the poor thing Ah no not to
de ternura María Patiño la pobre Ah no a
me now no more
m ahora ya no no
Black
Black
Friday stops accumulating things it makes me a
frid deja de acumular cosas a m me da un
little tender
poco de ternura